studyinholland.nl 2019-11-11

# Privacy policy — Study in Holland

We are aware that you have placed your trust in us. Therefore, we handle your personal data with the utmost care. How exactly do we do that? 

You register with a network, sign up for a training or subscribe to a newsletter. When you use one of our services, we ask you for your personal details, so that we can provide you with good service. These could be your name, address, email address and telephone number. 

## Use

We will use your personal data exclusively for the purpose for which you have provided it. If you entered your name and email address to subscribe to a newsletter, for example, we will not use the data to send you other information. Unless expressly stated otherwise, we will not pass on your personal data to third parties. Your data may be used by the authorities, if legally required.

If you ask us a question we may need to involve another organisation to answer this question. The data that we exchange with this organisation will only be used by them to answer your question.

When you subscribe to a newsletter, you can indicate a preference for certain topics. You will then only get to see news about those topics. We will save your preferences for as long as you are subscribed to the newsletter. 

## Under 16

If you are under 16 years of age your parents or guardians need to give us permission to process your personal data.

## Storage and protection

We do not store your personal data for longer than necessary. For example, if you cancel your subscription to one of our newsletters, we will delete your personal data. We will process and protect your personal data with due care. 

## Your data

You can request to see which data we have stored under your name, or ask for it to be amended or removed, using this form: 

For newsletters you can also use the online unsubscribe option. Your data will then be automatically removed from the mailing list of the newsletter.

## Exception

We cannot remove your data if we need them to carry out an agreement we have with you, or if we need to store your data for another reason. This is the case, for example, if you have applied for funding. When you apply for a job with us, we will store your information for the duration of the application procedure./

## Costs

A request to see or amend your data or to have your data removed is free, unless your request is manifestly unfounded or excessive. If that is the case, we can decide not to process your request, or charge you a fee for administrative costs of € 500 per request.  

## Do you have a complaint or objection?  

If you do not agree with the way we process your personal data, you can submit a complaint to Nuffic. You can read how to file a complaint in our [complaints procedure](https://www.nuffic.nl/contact/vraag-klacht-of-bezwaar/klachtenregeling). You can also submit your complaint to the [Dutch Data Protection Authority](https://autoriteitpersoonsgegevens.nl/en).

You can also object to the processing of your personal data if we process them on the basis of protection the legitimate interests of Nuffic or of a third party to whom we provide the data. You can find out how to do this by checking our

[objection procedure](https://www.nuffic.nl/contact/vraag-klacht-of-bezwaar/klachtenregeling).

## The Data Protection Officer

The Data Protection Officer (DPO) who supervises the application of and compliance with the GDPR at Nuffic is:

Ms Sjoera Nas (MA)  
 tel.: +31 70 4260 260

Ms Nas works as a senior adviser for Privacy Company in The Hague.

## Privacy policy amendments

We reserve the right to amend this privacy policy within the framework of the applicable laws and regulations relating to privacy and data protection, more specifically the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). We will inform you about any amendments in our privacy policy.
